I love it! I love it!
-Yes. -Ha-ha-ha.
I knew that'd get him! -Hey.
Hello? MAN : Walter?
Yes? -I have some bad news.
It's about your two uncles, son.
Walter?
Walter? Walter.
Good news.
You're spending the summer with your two uncles.
It's just gonna be for a few weeks. A month or two, tops.
Scout's honor, okay?
Cross my heart and hope to die, okay?
Where are you going this time?
The Fort Worth College of Court Reporting.
I met a guy last night.
He's gonna pull some strings.
Walter, you're gonna have to learn to trust people...
...or you're gonna grow up bitter and disappointed.
You're gonna have fun with your two uncles. You'll see.
Mom, you're an only child.
I know what uncles are.
Well, Mr. Smarty-Pants...
...it just so happens, they really are your uncles.
Your great-uncles.
My mother's brothers.
They disappeared 40 years ago...
...and just now showed up back here in Texas.
-Can't I come with you? -No.
Honey, I'm gonna be working my tail off learning court reporting.
I'm doing everything I can to keep this family together.
How about a little help here, okay?
Now, look.
They say these two old men got millions stashed away in cash.
Nobody knows where they got it.
Got no kids, no one to leave all that money to.
You and me, we're as close as any family they got.
You want them to like me...
...so they'll die and leave us their money?
We could buy a house, maybe settle down.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Oh, look. Here it is.
Here it is, honey. Here it is.
By the way, I hear these two were in some state nuthouse for 40 years.
Got all their money from a big lawsuit or something.
But then there's lots of stories about them.
Who knows what to believe?
Just find out where they stashed all that money, okay?
-Maybe we should've called first. -No. Older people just love surprises.
Here we are.
Okay.
Aah! Aah!
Go away, go away. Hey, go away. Shoo.
Show them you're friendly, honey. Let them smell your hand.
They must be down there by that lake.
Let's go. Come on.
Let's go. There he is.
Winged him. GARTH: He's running for it.
Damn. Empty. -Get ammo. I'll keep him covered.
Yoo-hoo.
Ha, ha.
Huh?
Yoo-hoo.
You send for a hooker?
Uncle Hub, Uncle Garth, it's me, Mae.
Mae.
Pearl's daughter.
And I brought Walter, your nephew.
-Relatives. -Damn, God.
We're old, damn it. Leave us alone.
The last thing we need is some little sissy boy...
...hanging around all summer.
Walter, honey...
...why don't you wait out here and play, okay? I'll be a minute.
He could help out around here, do chores.
Help out? Your kid's a damn wienie.
I know.
That's why he needs to be around real men...
...like you two. It won't be for long.
He's gotta cook for his damn self. I'm not cooking.
Nice doggie. Come play.
This is for your own good, Walter.
You know...
... I bet all that money is hidden real close by.
Imagine, a real buried treasure...
...just like in those books you're always reading.
Walter, maybe if you'd learn to smile once in a while...
...then people might like you.
Now, come on, how about a big smile to remember you by?
Okay? Come on.
You're gonna have to work on that smile while I'm gone, okay?
Bye, honey. Bye.
Well?
If my mom calls, can we hear the telephone out here?
-Don't have one. -No telephone?
Is it okay if I go inside and watch television?
-Ain't got one. -No television?
What do you do?
Hey.
Rumor has is you two have millions stashed away.
Why not put some of that money to work for you...
...with the high yield only investing in gold and silver can bring?
Can I leave you some pamphlets?
Gentlemen, word is out.
You are two sophisticated men of means--
Hey!
Nice evening. Peaceful.